[{"question": "Computer Vandalism is an  _______  of physical destroying computing resources using physical force or malicious\r code.", "answer": "Act", "answer_index": 3, "shuffled": ["Social Event", "Nonevent", "Miracle", "Act", "Happening", "Group Action"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "An example of salami  _______ \r is gaining access to online banking of an individual and withdrawing amount in such a small\r amounts that it remains unnoticed by the owner.", "answer": "Attack", "answer_index": 5, "shuffled": ["Ruff", "Down", "Innings", "Move", "Lead", "Attack"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "These  _______  of attacks are usually performed by professional criminals, by a\r country on other rival countries, politicians to damage the image of the rival person or\r the country, terrorists, rival companies, etc.", "answer": "Types", "answer_index": 3, "shuffled": ["Brachycephalic", "Man", "Professional", "Types", "Stay-at-home", "Militarist"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "These types of attacks are usually performed by professional criminals, by a\r country on other rival countries, politicians to damage the  _______  of the rival person or\r the country, terrorists, rival companies, etc.", "answer": "Image", "answer_index": 1, "shuffled": ["Libra", "Image", "Sniffler", "Amateur", "Reliever", "Termer"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "There is a full  _______  of malwares which can seriously degrade\r the performance of the host machine.", "answer": "Range", "answer_index": 5, "shuffled": ["Source", "Airfield", "Menagerie", "Gas System", "Forum", "Range"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "There are various types of malwares present in\r the  _______ .", "answer": "Internet", "answer_index": 3, "shuffled": ["Intelnet", "Wide Area Network", "Local Area Network", "Internet", "Intranet", "World Wide Web"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "If the conditions holds true in future, the malicious action begins\r and based on the action defined in the malicious code, they either destroy the information\r stored in the  _______  or make  _______  unusable.", "answer": "System", "answer_index": 2, "shuffled": ["Furnishing", "Connection", "System", "Container", "Hardware", "Medium"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "If the conditions holds true in future, the malicious  _______  begins\r and based on the  _______  defined in the malicious code, they either destroy the information\r stored in the system or make system unusable.", "answer": "Action", "answer_index": 5, "shuffled": ["Degeneration", "Iteration", "Organic Process", "Shaping", "Human Process", "Action"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "Computer Vandalism is an act of physical destroying computing resources using physical force or malicious\r  _______ .", "answer": "Code", "answer_index": 1, "shuffled": ["Prescription", "Code", "Writing", "Reading", "Print", "Transcription"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "An example of salami attack\r is gaining  _______  to online banking of an individual and withdrawing amount in such a small\r amounts that it remains unnoticed by the owner.", "answer": "Access", "answer_index": 0, "shuffled": ["Access", "Privilege", "Advowson", "Water Right", "Grant", "Floor"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "This\r software modifies the browsers setting and redirect  _______  to other unintentional sites.", "answer": "Links", "answer_index": 2, "shuffled": ["Toggle", "System Error", "Links", "Call", "Command Line", "Link"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "It is comparitively easy for an  _______  to perform a\r cyber attack as he is well aware of the policies, processes, IT architecture and\r wealness of the security system.", "answer": "Insider", "answer_index": 4, "shuffled": ["President", "Chief Financial Officer", "Chief Executive Officer", "Chairman Of The Board", "Insider"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "The term cyber crime is used to describe a unlawful  _______  in which computer or computing\r devices such as smartphones, tablets, Personal Digital Assistants(PDAs), etc.", "answer": "Activity", "answer_index": 4, "shuffled": ["Judgment", "Rejection", "Proclamation", "Production", "Activity", "Derivation"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "This\r software modifies the  _______  setting and redirect links to other unintentional sites.", "answer": "Browsers", "answer_index": 5, "shuffled": ["Browser", "Active Application", "Applet", "Job", "Word Processor", "Browsers"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "The purpose of phishing is\r  _______  and the personal information like username, password, and credit card number\r etc.", "answer": "Identity theft", "answer_index": 5, "shuffled": ["Swindle", "Election Fraud", "Intrinsic Fraud", "Fraud In The Factum", "Mail Fraud", "Identity theft"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "This\r  _______  modifies the browsers setting and redirect links to other unintentional sites.", "answer": "Software", "answer_index": 3, "shuffled": ["American Standard Code For Information Interchange", "Address", "Operation Code", "Software", "Machine Code", "Firmware"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "An expreicend  _______ /security administrator keeps regual eye on the log\r generated by the firewalls as extertnal attacks can be traced out by carefully analysinig\r these firewall logs.", "answer": "Network", "answer_index": 0, "shuffled": ["Network", "Explosive Detection System", "Data System", "Inertial Guidance System", "Audio System", "Scaffolding"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "There is a full range of malwares which can seriously degrade\r the  _______  of the host machine.", "answer": "Performance", "answer_index": 1, "shuffled": ["Masterstroke", "Performance", "Going", "Arrival", "Fait Accompli", "Beachhead"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "Malware stands for \u201cMalicious Software\u201d and it is designed to gain access or installed into the\r computer without the consent of the  _______ .", "answer": "User", "answer_index": 0, "shuffled": ["User", "Jat", "Smasher", "Amateur", "Aquarius", "Waker"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}, {"question": "These types of attacks are usually performed by professional criminals, by a\r country on other rival countries, politicians to damage the image of the rival  _______  or\r the country, terrorists, rival companies, etc.", "answer": "Person", "answer_index": 0, "shuffled": ["Person", "Power", "Cause Of Death", "Catalyst", "Vital Principle", "Destiny"], "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F"]}]